Irving P. Krick papers, 1921-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Paris Operations
  - Organization (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Itineraries and transportation (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous weather charts, Paris and Lyon (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Morocco and Tunisia (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - SODETEP: Contracts (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Prospect: Zurich (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Val D'Isere, France (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Contracts: Lyon (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Nomination of corporation officers (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Contracts, Consulat General de France a Denver (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: David Wharry (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and proposals (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Project organization (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Visas (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Administration and organization (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Proposals: Tunis (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Addresses (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Tunisia newspapers (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Operations (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Personal
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics - Award of Recognition (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hotel receipts (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Hotel receipts (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Airline ticket stubs (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Announcements and articles regarding Krick as pianist (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Articles: Krick, nuclear bomb testing, and weather (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Photograph of an unidentified woman (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Research Papers
  - Major Problems Facing Weather Modification Today, by the Weather Modification Council (California) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - A Meteorological and Oceanographic Analysis of the Passage of the S.S. Warrior, by Louis Allen (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Note on the Frequency of Soft Hail in Central Alberta, Peter W. Summers (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Cloud Photogrammetry, J.H. Renick and R.H. Douglas (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Ice Nuclei and Convective Storms, George A. Isaac (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - An Introduction to the Evaluation of Agricultural Cloud Seeding Projects Using Space Age Technology, by Krick (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - An Introduction to the Evaluation of Cloud Seeding Projects Using Space Age Technology, by Krick (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Fog Prevention at Airports, by Krick (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Predicting the Weather for the Long Term (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Synoptic Survey of the 1965 Hail Season in Alberta, by C.E. Thompson (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Synoptic Survey of the 1967 Hail Season in Alberta, by D.B. Currie and R.A.D. Dewar (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Time-Dependent Characteristics of the Heterogeneous Nucleation of Ice, by Gabor Vali and E.J. Stansbury (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Hail Research at McGill, 1965-71, by Stormy Weather Group (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Wind Measurements Near Alberta Hail Storms, 1966-67, by N.H. Thyer (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Numerical Simulation of Large Convective Clouds, by Takao Takeda (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Quantitative Hailstorm Studies Using Broad Vertical-Beam Radar, by Jerry Pell (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Hail Storm of 29 June 1967, by Stormy Weather Group (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Further Studies on the Effects of Precipitation on Convection, F. Ian Harris (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Weather Radar Studies, by J. Stewart Marshall (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Life-Cycle of a Summer Storm from Radar Records, by Clifford D. Holtz (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Convective Overturning and Summer Storms, by J. Stewart Marshall (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Alberta Hail Studies 1966, by Stormy Weather Group (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Studies of the Formation of Precipitation in Convection, by Stormy Weather Group (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Measurements of Snowfall by Radar, by Paul E. Carlson (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Alberta Hail Studies 1968 Field Program, by James H. Renick (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Report of the Special Committee on Crop Insurance and Weather Modification, Alberta (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Statistical Analysis of Weather Modification Experiments, by Edward J. Wegman and Douglas J. DePriest (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - NOAA Report on the Southern California Floods, Flash Floods, and Mudslides of Feb 8- 10, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Report No. 5: Test of Analogue Selection by the Use of a Subcategorical Method of Map Classification (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Strategic Weather Services
  - Meeting minutes and other documents (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Brochures (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - AKZO Phase One Report (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Charming Shoppes Inc. Monthly Forecast (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Quaker Oats Co., Sample Monthly Forecast (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Weekly temperature forecast, various U.S. cities (Box 111, Folder 9)
- U.S. Government
  - Project Skywater: Annual Report, U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Project Skywater: Annual Report, U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearing on U.S. Senate Bills S.2916 and S.23 relating to Weather Modification (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Weather Modification Grants, U.S. Senate Hearing (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Implementation of the Climate Act, U.S. Senate Hearing (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Weather Modification, U.S. Senate Hearing (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Weather Modification, U.S. Senate Hearing (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Drought Emergency Relief Act of 1976, U.S. Senate Hearing (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Weather Modification and Control: A Report to the U.S. Senate (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Weather Modification Senate Hearings on Bills S.23 and S.2916, Part I (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Senate Bill S.2058, with Krick statement (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - House of Representatives Bill HR.4200 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Public Works Appropriations, U.S. Senate Hearings, HR.9220, part 3 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - House of Representatives, Committee on Agriculture, HR.12083 and correspondence (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Weather Modification, Senate Hearings on S.23 and S.2916, Part 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Water Resources Activities in the U.S., Impact of New Techniques, Senate Bill S.Res.48 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Experimental Research Program in Cloud Modification, Senate Hearings on S.86 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Special Report to the President and Congress: The Future of the Nation's Weather Services (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Weather Modification, Senate Hearings on S.23 and S.2916, Part 2 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Weather Modification, Senate Hearings on S.373 and S.2058 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Weather Control and Augmented Potable Water Supply, Joint Hearings, U.S. Senate on S.5, S.222, and S.798 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Project Skywalker '70, Bureau of Reclamation's Program (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Weather Modification Project
  - Foreign Prospect: Libya (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Prospect: Lebanon (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Prospect: Korea (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Prospect: Japan (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Prospect: Italy (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Prospect: Jamaica (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Prospect: Israel (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Prospect: Morocco (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Prospect: Mexico (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Young, Throckmorton, Shakelford, and Stephens Counties, Texas (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Washington (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Active Client: Woods County, Texas (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local Prospect: California (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local Prospect: Louisiana (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Prospect: Various (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Major County, Oklahoma (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: Isabella County, Michigan (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local Prospect: Northwest (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local Prospect: Northwest (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local Prospect: Northwest (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Big Bed Water Devil Corporation (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local Prospect: Ortonville and Big Stone County, Minnesota (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local Prospect: Ortonville and Big Stone County, Minnesota (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Barry County, California (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Menominee County, Michigan (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Branch County, Michigan (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local Prospect: American Sugar Cane League (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Red River, New Mexico (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Active Client: Calhoun County, Michigan (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Active Client: Isabella County (Second Half), Michigan (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Michiana Weather Incorporated, Michigan (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Active Client: St. Joseph County, Michigan (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Lawton, Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Lawton, Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Arbuckle Counties, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Active Client: Washita County, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Active County: Kiowa County, Oklahoma (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Active Client: Twin Falls, Idaho (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Albert, New Mexico (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: Roswell, New Mexico (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local Prospect: California, New Mexico, and Colarado - Various (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local Prospect: California, New Mexico, and Colorado - Various (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Prospect: Iran (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Prospect: Iran (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local Prospect: California (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local Prospect: California (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local Prospect: California (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local Prospect: California - Parsons (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local Prospect: California - News clippings (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Local Prospect: California - Mobil Oil Company (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Prospect: Germany (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Prospect: French West Indies (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Prospect: Formosa - Bureau of Food, Power and Light (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Prospect: France (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Prospect: England (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Prospect: Egypt (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Prospect: Ecuador (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Prospect: Dominican Republic (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Prospect: Cuba (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Prospect: China (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa - De Wit (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Prospect: Australia (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Prospect: Australia (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Prospect: Algeria (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Prospect: Argentina (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Local Prospect: California - Western Oil and Gas Association (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Local Prospect: Sharon, Oklahoma (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Prospect: Australia (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Business Plan (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous materials (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous materials (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Prospect: Spain - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Prospect: Spain - Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Prospect: Spain - Articles of Association and Agreements with Ministries of Agriculture and Air (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fuels - General (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hydro Energy Prospects (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Prospect: Canada (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Generator - Salt Equipment, Some materials burned by fire. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Fuels - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Generator - Coke Model 16 Equipment (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Nuclei Counter - Stationary Equipment (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Storm Study (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hypothetical AGI Ground Generator (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hail Study Forms: Alberta, Canada (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ice Crystal Deposition: Alberta, Canada (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Base Maps: Delaware (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Base Maps: California (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Base Maps: Michigan (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Base Maps: Minnesota (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Base Maps: Northcentral Texas (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Base Maps: Oklahoma (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Precipitation Charts: Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Summary of Rain Increase: Michigan (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Crop Yield: Michigan (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Base Maps: Colorado, Some materials fire damaged. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Base Maps: Texas (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Base Maps: Washington (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Base Maps: Alberta, Canada (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Base Maps: British Columbia, Canada (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Base Maps: Louisiana (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Base Maps: Louisiana (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Precipitation Analysis Maps: Michigan (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Silver Iodide Plume Chart (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Precipitation Data: Louisiana (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Storm Studies: Michigan (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Precipitation Analysis Maps: Michigan (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Generator Location Map: Louisian (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Generator Location Map: Oklahoma (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Precipitation Analysis Maps: New Mexico (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Data: Alberta, Canada (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Base Maps: Louisiana (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fuels (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Prospect: Spain - Correspondence with Roberto Sanches (Confidential) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Local Prospect: Vella Road - Papers, plans and lease. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: University of Illinois (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Louisiana (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Active Client: Operation Snowflake Inc. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Local Prospect: New Mexico (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Beaver County, Oklahoma (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Local Prospect: New Mexico (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Mitchell Bell Ranches, New Mexico (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Central Minnesota (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Adams County, Iowa (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Active Client: Adams County, Iowa (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Active Client: Adams County, Iowa (3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Custer County, Oklahoma (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: Big Stone Weather Inc, Minnesota (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Ellis County, Oklahoma (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Active Client: Natchitoches Parish Water Committee, Louisiana (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Active Client: Ellendale, Delaware (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Local Prospect: Virginia (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Local Prospect: Texas (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Prospect: Africa (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Alberta, Canada - Organization and plans (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Active Client: Alberta, Canada - Organization and plans (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Alberta, Canada (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Interim Weather Modification Board (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Interim Weather Modification Board (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local Prospect: Edwards Underground Water District, Texas (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local Prospect: San Angelo, Texas (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: Alberta, Canada (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Denver, Colorado (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Active Client: Sauk Centre, Minnesota (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Active Client: Concordia Water Resources Development - Concordia, Louisiana (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Los Angeles County, California (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Report: Oklahoma Farm and Ranch Areas (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Harvey's Peanut Company, Georgia (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local Prospect: Louisiana (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local Prospect: Louisiana (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Project: Northeast New Mexico (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Australia (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Active Client: MD of Kneehill (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Active Client: Mountain View County, Alberta, Canada (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Active Client: Santa Ana River Corp., Redlands, California (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - A Submission to the Government of Alberta by Alberta Weather Modification Co-op (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: El Dorado, Kansas (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Active Client: Northwest Iowa Rain Increase Association (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Company, Spokane, Washington (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Active Client: Power and Light Co., Portland, Oregon (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Washington Water Power Co., Spokane, Washington (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Prospect: Syria (Correspondence with Pierre Mamarbachi) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Maps: Wheatland County, Alberta, Canada (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Map: Kneehill County, Alberta, Canada (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Map: Mountain View, Alberta, Canada (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Map: Starland Municipal District Map, Alberta, Canada (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Maps: New South Wales, Australia (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Map: Queensland, Australi (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Map: Powell River Company map of property, British Columbia (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - World map (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Active Client: Alberta Hall Studies (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Active Client: Dr. T.A. Peterson, Alberta, Canada (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hail news release (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (3 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (1 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (2 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (3 of 3) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Alberta research, with correspondence regarding license permits and federal regulations (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Research: Crop forecasts, rough drafts (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alberta Agricultural Research Trust, Professor T.A. Peterson (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (1 of 3) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (2 of 3) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (3 of 3) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Jim Bishop (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Jim Bishop (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Intera, Alberta (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - List of unnumbered reports (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Alberta Hail Research: Jim Bishop (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Calgary, Alberta, Canada (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Alberta Government (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Cepansa contract (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Cepansa contract (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Client: Sodetep contract, Algeria (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Client: Cassa contract, Italy (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Active Client: Rocky View, Alberta (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Active Client: Starland Weather Modification Association, Alberta (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Wheatland Association, Alberta (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Active Client: Rocky View Association, Alberta (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Research Council of Alberta (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Active Client: Guadaloupe, Brussels, Belgium (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Union Miniere du Haut-Katanga, Africa (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Active Client: Belgium (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Active Client: Mountain View Association (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - City of Calgary (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Clients: La Companie des Bananes, Africa (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Active Client: Guadalupe National Park (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Client: Australi (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Active Client: Quaker Oats (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Alberta: Miscellaneous documents (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Active Client: Sunoco contract (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Report for Natchitoches Parish, Louisiana (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Foreign prospect: South Africa (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: American Water Works Service Company (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Weather Modification Operation for Los Angeles County Flood Control District (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Contract: State of Colorado (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: Northeast Louisiana Water Corporation. Louisisana (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Contract: The Diamond A Cattle Company, New Mexico (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Big Band Water Development Company, Washington (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: International Paper Company, Alabama (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Horse Heaven Water Development Corporation, Washington (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Horse Heaven Water Development Corporation, Washington (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Union Pacific Railroad Company, Utah (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Union Pacific Railroad Company, Utah, and Sun Valley Lodge, Idaho (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Contracts: C.V. Griffin Groves Company, Florida (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: C.V. Griffin Groves Company, Florida (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Grand Mesa Water Users Association, Colorado (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Grand Mesa Water Users Association, Colorado (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Grand Mesa Water Users Association, Colorado (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: Brekenridge Land Incorporated, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Brekendridge Land Incorporated, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Winter Park, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Winter Park, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: Aspen Cloud Seeding Fund, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Aspen Cloud Seeding Fund, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Contracts: Central Minnesota Weather Incorporated, Minnesota (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: T.E. Mitchell and Son Incorporated, New Mexico (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Campbell Farming Corporation, Montana (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: T.O. Ranch Company, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Vail Associated Limited, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Vail Associated Limited, Colorado (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: M-Card Incorporated, Michigan (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: M-Card Incorporated, Michigan (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Contract: Don Chemical Company, Freeport Division, Texas (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Don Chemical Company, Freeport Division, Texas (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Contract: McGregor Land and Livestock Company, Washington (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: McGregor Land and Livestock Company, Washington (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: Eureka Weather Development Corporation, Washington (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Eureka Weather Development Corporation, Washington (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Bonneville Power Administration, Colorado (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: South Louisiana Agricultural Improvement Association (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Pacific Power and Light Company, Oregon (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: William Tonn and Sons, Montana (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Contracts: Toole County Rural Development Association, Montana (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Toole County Rural Development Association, Montana (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Contract: Tri-Counties Rural Development Association, Montana (Box 29, Folder 11)